### Contact

shalomdmello@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/fiona-d-mello-1a3313166 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Web Development Machine Learning Mathematics

### Certifications

Data Science & Analytics Career Paths & Certifications: First Steps

# Fiona D'mello

Systems Engineer at Infosys

Pune, Maharashtra, India

## Summary

Trained to be a Full Stack Web Application Developer (MERN), I currently work as a Full Stack Mobile Application developer, with hands on experience in - React Native, PostgresSQL and the multiple services provided by AWS.

I find myself immensely interested in the fields of Data Analysis, Machine Learning and AI. And as an appreciator of self acquired knowledge, you will find me spending time trying to acquire skills in my fields of interest during weekends! A passionately-dedicated, hard working, self-learner I like to keep myself pushing to find ways to solve problems even when I seem to be at my wits end.

# Experience

Infosys
Systems Engineer
January 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Pune

Shri Devi Institute of Technology Assistant Professor February 2018 - May 2018 (4 months) Mangalore

## Education

Manipal Institute of Technology Master's degree, Physics · (2015 - 2017)